Now we want to create our fun function.
现在我们要创建我们的 "fund" 函数
And then later on, we're going to create our withdrawal function.
稍后我们还要创建我们的 "withdraw" 函数
And this is where front end JavaScript code. And no Gs are a little bit different.
这里的是前端 JavaScript 代码，它和 Node.js 有一些小的不同
In no JS, we've been using this require keyword to import dependencies
在 Node.js 中，我们一直用的是 `require` 关键字来导入依赖库
in front end JavaScript,  you can't use require, and it won't exactly work.
而在前端 JavaScript 中，就不能使用 `require` 了，它是完全不工作的
Now later on, we're going to use the Import keyword,
现在，我们要使用 `import` 关键字
which is really the better way to do this.
它其实是处理这些操作更好的方式
And this is where our first differences going to be
这就是我们所遇到的第一处不同
using the Import keyword for front end is much better than the require keyword,
在前端中使用 `import` 关键字要比使用 `require` 关键字好一些
especially since the require keyword doesn't actually work.
尤其是 `require` 关键字其实并不能使用
And for those you who might struggle with this disconnect in this change.
你们中的有些对此感到困惑人可能会对这种变化产生一些撕裂感
Once again, in the GitHub repo associated with this,
所以再次强调，在与课程关联的 GitHub 仓库中
we do have a Node js edition of this,
我们还提供了 Node.js 版本的代码
where you can use the require keyword,
你可以在这里使用 `require` 关键字
you just have to go through the readme and download some packages and run some scripts
你只需要阅读一下 "README"，并下载一些包，然后运行一些脚本
that basically transform your code that uses require into code that works with imports.
这些脚本基本上就是将使用 `require` 的代码给转换为使用 `import`
But we're going to teach you the way to work with your front end code here using imports.
但我们的教学方式是直接在前端代码中使用 `import`
Now you'll see when we get to next Jas
之后你会看到，当我们进入到 Next.js 时
that we will still download code from node modules
我们仍然会从 "node_modules" 中下载代码
and using a yarn lock and a package json etc.
并且仍然会使用 "yarn.lock" 和 "package.json" 等文件
So summary in future seconds, we are still going to do yarn add.
所以归根结底，我们在未来仍然会继续使用 `yarn add`
But outside of a framework
但在这个框架之外，
when we're using this raw JavaScript, this raw HTML setup, like what we're working with here,
当我们使用原始的 JavaScript 和原始的 HTML 设置时，比如我们现在这样
we're not going to be doing yarn, add node modules
我们就不能使用 `yarn add node_modules` 了
will add node modules for framework like next react.
未来我们还是会在诸如 "Next React" 等框架中继续使用 "node_modules"
But for raw JavaScript, we'll be using a different syntax,
但在原始的 JavaScript 中，我们会使用不同的语法
which I'll show you soon.
我马上就会展示这一点
So let's go ahead and start building our fund function here.
让我们继续，开始在这里构建我们的 "fund" 函数吧
To make our fun functions, what would we normally do?
为了构建我们的 "fund" 函数，我们通常是怎么做的呢？
Well, we'd create an async function called fund.
我们要创建一个 `async function` 名为 `fund()`
And in this function, we probably would want to take some ether mount as a parameter,
在这个函数中，我们大概想让它接收一些 "ethAmount" 作为参数
because we're going to want to fund it with some amount of Aetherium.
因为我们要用一定数额的以太币来进行资助
When we call this function, we might want to run console dot log
当我们调用这个函数时，我们可能想要运行 `console.log(``)`
will do a little string interpolation here.
我们要在这里做一个字符串插值
Funding with eth amount, dot dot dot,
`Funding with $...`
these semicolons are going to drive me absolutely insane.
这些分号绝对会让我疯掉
So I'm going to add a our dot prettier dot our rc file into this,
所以我要在这里添加一个 ".prettierrc" 文件
and I'm going to go ahead and add prettier in here. Otherwise, I'm going to lose my mind.
我要在这里添加 "prettier"，否则我会失去理智的
So we're gonna do yarn add dash dash Dev, prettier,
所以我们来执行 `yarn add --dev prettier`
just so we can format our JavaScript with prettier
这样我们就能使用 "prettier" 来格式化我们的 JavaScript 了
come back to index.js. I'm gonna hit command S,
回到 "index.js"，按下 "Command S"
and it looks like it does indeed, auto format with prettier now yay, no matter semicolons,
看起来它确实使用 "prettier" 进行自动格式化了，耶，没有分号了
we can call this fun function the same way we call connect.
我们可以像调用 "connect()" 函数一样调用这个 "fund()" 函数
So in in our index dot HTML, maybe we'll create a new button.
所以在我们的 "index.html" 中，我们需要创建一个新的按钮
Button. We'll give it an ID of fund will say on click equals fund.
``
And we'll say fund. And this will be our button here,
接着是 `Fund` 最后是 ``
we save it, we're looking at our front end.
我们保存一下，然后再看看我们的前端
Now the fund button that if we call, we say funding with undefined
现在就有了一个 "Fund" 按钮，如果我们调用它就会收到 "Funding with undefined"
because we're not passing it an amount here.
因为我们这里并没有给它任何金额
So back in our index console dot log funding with
所以回到我们 "index" 的 `console.log(`Funding with`)`
and we'll just want to make sure that we can actually call that Funmi function.
我们只需要确保我们能够实际调用那个 "FundMe()" 函数即可
So we'll copy this line again and we'll say type of window dot Aetherium does not equal undefined.
所以我们再次复制这一行 `typeof window.ethereum !== "undefined"`
We'll go ahead and try to fund here
并在这里继续编写 "fund" 函数
to send a transaction. What are the things that we absolutely 100% Always need?
要发送一笔交易，有什么东西是我们百分之百肯定需要的？
Well, we need a provider slash connection to the blockchain.
我们需要一个 "provider" 或者说连接到区块链上 ("/ connection to the blockchain")
And we need a signer slash wallet, slash someone with some gas to actually send it
我们还需要一个 "signer / wallet" 或者说一个具有 gas 的人("/ some with some gas") 以实际发送交易
and then And we're probably going to need the contract that we are interacting with.
接着我们很可能还需要一个“能够与之交互的合约”("contract that we are interacting with")
And to get that contract, we're going to need ABI and address.
为了获取这个合约，我们需要 "ABI" 还有地址 ("address")
And with these all together, we can send any transaction.
有了这些，我们就可以发送任何交易了
So to get our provider, we're going to actually go ahead and work with ethers again.
为了获取我们的 "provider"，我们要再次用到 ethers
Now, we're going to do it a little bit differently, though,
现在，我们将以略微有点不同的方式来进行操作
before, the way we worked with ethers is we said const ethers equals require ethers, right.
之前我们使用 ethers 的方法是 `const  = require("ethers")` 对吧？
And this is how we pulled ethers.
这就是我们获取 ethers 的方式
And now like I just said to you, though,
现在，就像我刚才跟你说的那样
require doesn't work in the front end.
`require` 在前端中并不适用
And we actually don't want to install ethers with a node modules package.
而且我们并不想通过 "node_modules" 包来安装 ethers
So what we can actually do instead
所以我们可以采用另一种方法
is let's go to the ethers documentation.
让我们前往 ethers 的文档
If you go to the Getting Started section, scroll down,
如果你点开这个 "Getting Started" 部分，往下拉
they have a section about importing using Node js, which uses require or imports.
他们在这里有一个 "Importing" 部分，Node.js 下，可以使用 `require` 或 `import`
And then they also have some documentation for working with the web browser.
接下来，他们还有一个在 “Web 浏览器”("Web Browser")下的使用文档
So instead of us doing a node module, what we'll do
所以我们不再使用 "node_modules"
is we'll copy the ethers library to our own directories and serve it ourselves.
而是把 ethers 库复制到我们的目录中，自行使用服务
So what we do is we can come in here, we can copy this massive file,
我们可以到这里来，复制这个巨大的文件
which is ethers, but in front end addition,
这个文件就是 ethers，只不过是前端版本
and come back to our file. And we'll make a new file in here.
回到我们的文件这里，然后创建一个新的文件
Called ethers. We'll do 5.6 point esm.min.js.
命名为 "ethers-5.6.esm.min.js"
And we'll paste that massive thing in here.
接着我们把这一大堆内容粘贴到这里来
Now, since I have prettier
现在，由于我拥有 "prettier" 扩展
when I save it, it's going to auto format.
所以当我保存时，它就会自动进行格式化
And it's just this huge file, which has everything ethers,
这是一个巨--大的文件，其中包含了 ethers 的所有内容
but front end defied if you will.
但却是前端化的
Now what we can do is we can import this into our index.js.
现在我们就可以将其导入到我们的 "index.js" 里了
So instead of using require in here, we'll say import ethers from
所以我们就不在这里使用 `require` 了，而是 `import  from "./"`
and then we'll just refer to that file that we just got ethers dash 5.6 point esm.min.js.
然后指向我们刚刚获取的那个文件 `"ethers-5.6.esm.min.js"`
Now, we only need to do this weird copy pasting of the file import thing in this HTML JavaScript lesson.
现在，我们只会在这个 HTML JavaScript 课程中，使用这种奇怪的复制粘贴文件再导入的方式
In future lessons with Node js, we are going to do yarn, add ethers,
在未来使用 Node.js 的课程中，我们还是会使用 `yarn add ethers`
kinda like we've normally seen.
就和我们平常看到的一样
The frameworks like React and next Jas that we're going to use
之后我们要使用的 "React" 和 "Next.js" 框架
are going to automatically convert those yarn added packages to their front end to five versions.
会把它们用 yarn 添加的包自动转换为适用前端的版本
But for this section, this is how we're going to actually import the ethers package.
但在本节中，这就是我们导入 ethers 包的方式
Now the other thing we'll have to do
现在我们还得处理另外一件事
is on our front end, we'll have to change this from type text slash JavaScript to type module
在我们的前端中，我们要把这个 `type="text/javascript"` 修改为 `type="module"`
changes. The type module allows us to import modules into our code,
修改为 `type="module"` 可以允许我们在代码中导入模块
which we're going to be importing this, and we're going to import another module as well.
我们要导入这个，以及另外一个模块
Awesome.
非常好
And now though, if we go back to our front end,
现在如果回到我们的前端
do a little refresh with the connect button,
刷新一下，然后点击 "Connect"
we get Connect is not defined at HTML button.on. Click,
我们会被提示 “connect 未在 HTMLButtonElement.onclick 中被定义”
("connect is not defined at HTMLButtonElement.onclick")
so instead of calling our Connect button from the front end here,
所以我们不再继续在前端中调用 "Connect" 按钮了
we're going to remove these on clicks from our index dot HTML,
而是把这些 "onclick" 从 "index.html" 中都删掉
and go into our index.js and add those connect buttons in here.
然后来到我们的 "index.js"，并把 "Connect" 按钮添加到这里
So we'll say const. Connect button equals document, dot get element by ID, Connect button.
`const connectButton = document.getElementById("connectButton")`
And then we'll say const. One button equals Doc, you meant dot get element by ID. One button,
然后是 `const fundButton = document.getElementById("fundButton")
the idea of the connect button is Connect button.
"Connect" 按钮的 "id" 就是 "connectButton"
The idea the fun button is fun button.
"Fund" 按钮的 "id" 就是 "fundButton"
And then we'll say connect button.on Click equals connect.
现在我们要写 `connectButton.onclick = connect`
And one button.on Click equals fond.
以及 `fundButton.onclick = fund`
We go back to our front end, do a little refresh. We'll hit connect now.
回到我们的前端，刷新一下，点击 "Connect"
And it's actually working,
它已经正常运行了
we'll go to our Metamask will disconnect, refresh, hit Connect,
打开我们的 MetaMask，断开连接，刷新，点击 "Connect"
and boom, it's popping up again.
嘭，它再次弹出来了
This is just due to that type being module,
这一切都是由于这里改成了 `type="module"`
if it was text slash JavaScript, that on click button adding in here,
如果这里还是 "text/javascript"，"onclick" 按钮就要添加在这里
but since we're doing module,
但是由于我们使用了模块("module")
we're going to add those on clicks right in our JavaScript.
我们就可以把这些 "onclick" 添加到我们的 JavaScript 里了
But now that we've got ethers in here,
但现在我们已经在这里有 ethers 了
what we can do is we can even do like a little console dot log, just paste ethers in here,
所以我们甚至可以在这里写 `console.log(ethers)`
or actually better yet.
或者更好的方式是
We'll add it right above the Connect button.
把它添加到 "connect" 按钮的上面
Go back to our front end, we'll do a refresh
回到我们的前端，刷新一下
and we see the entire ethers object right in our front end which is perfect,
我们可以看到，整个 ethers 对象现在就在我们的前端里，简直完美
which is exactly what we want here.
这正是我们想要看到的
And since we've got these two variables here, we might as well update this
因为我们这里有这两个变量了，所以我们不妨更新一下这里
to just say connect button dot innerHTML equals connected
直接就说 `connectButton.innerHTML = "Connected"`
and here as well. Connects button dot innerHTML equals please install meta mask
这里也是 `connectButton.innerHTML = "Please install MetaMask"`
because now connect button is going to be the same as running this document dot get element by ID right here.
因为现在 `connectButton` 就相当于运行这里的 `document.getElementById`